Hey guys, it’s Dave, if you’re here on
my Patreon page, it means that you’re considering
supporting me in my quest to educate the world.
I want to raise the bar of science literacy
in our society, and I sure could use your help.
Unlike some of the bigger educational channels,
I don’t have a staff, I don’t have any
grants or funding, this is a low-budget one-man show.
I write, edit, and animate all the content
on my channel, while managing all other aspects
of being an entrepreneur.
It’s a lot of work, and I’m usually at
it about sixty or seventy hours a week, so
calling it my passion is an understatement.
The problem is that the ad revenue I earn
from my YouTube channel is nowhere near commensurate
with the work I put in.
Even with tens of thousands of views per day,
it’s just not a living wage.
Beyond that, I have to pay people to check
my scripts for errors, operate camera and
audio when I shoot the content, and all kinds
of other things, so I sure could use some
help covering those costs.
If I can get enough support from you guys,
the viewers who benefit from all this hard
work, I can even hire people to help with
some of the writing and animating, which means
I could move much faster, and put out twice
as much content every week.
Even though I’ve already covered a lot of
topics, from chemistry to biology to physics
and tons more, there are still so many other
subjects left to do, and I’m not going to
stop until I do them all.
So please check out the rewards on this page.
For just a few dollars a month you can get
access to exclusive material, live chatting
with me, you can vote on what subjects I cover
next, or even get one-on-one tutoring.
These are just some of the ways I want to
thank you guys for taking the initiative to
help when you didn’t even have to, because
that’s how we are going to create the world
we all want to live in.
I’ll see you on YouTube.